The President was Amazing 49 questions and answers have
said to please let us know
what effect it will have on the insurance sector. The MD and CEO of the country
's leading insurance company Adidas
Life, Vivah Pradhan ji, is
always attending the program. She took out time
here on the big day of her budget.
Tell me the elements that the Finance Minister
talked about opening, 49 praised 74 percent seven
more, how to understand it
for the tractor, that
you thank you ji, half full welcome
because for a long time the industry otherwise needs to have
positive and the rest of these are quite
involved in these sectors, salute
because of this it will happen that especially the mid-career
companies which are still quite troubled, they
need capital, so now reduce
relaxation and gift director
investment camp comment now 217 4% there are some
conditions internal 50% now board being
independent etc. but at present it does
not seem so much owners, it is absolutely straightforward, find great
but will feel good, very liquid
clearance filler companies and the second thing is
that long-term infrastructure pending
and investment position  Government orders and
insurance are very super because our
policies 2030, these role policies, so please keep going
there, which can help in
nation building. A person was reading another provision,
he brought up a
chip, if you show it to me,
I want to get an opinion on it. To
analyze the tracks, the Finance
Minister said that those who
invest up to Rs 1 lakh can subscribe to it.
I am yet to see the fine print,
but if it is true that Dubai decided not to do it, then
what happens to each other, but let's not
look at it like this: we will buy term insurance. We
wanted to do a subscription policy for investment,
but the limit is quite big. But now we will
see that there is a
small subscription
product employed in the war, that too, it
invests money in the equity market and debt market.
Like the Twitter front, there is no difference in it
that you can take out a term plan separately. So,
I think the
era of subscribing to the channel is over.
I am very good at subscribing. I think the
big drawback is that
now our company address has changed.
Life revenue speaker this select 114 office in that
too this flag premium slide
donic bacterial infection but one leg
is disconnected statement speak and write its
capital requirement for which is
enough and if you will do the difference between these two
with mutual funds then here
cent is another aspect
pulling charges be next to nothing
absolutely all charges important second one
thing is unit linked insurance companies of
without entry if any surrender correct
in mutual fund that is not there morning have to give
for a person guarantee wide and bailouts
very difficult comparison cannot be
selected based on definitely that its
requirement is different due to which
investment will discover with the stars
are one of